- id: k-joyo-80c3
  prompt: "Meanings: stomach, paunch, crop\nOnyomi: イ"
  answers:
    - 胃
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7570
  prompt: "Meanings: uncommon, different, queerness\nOnyomi: イ\nKunyomi: こと, こと.なる, け"
  answers:
    - 異
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-907a
  prompt: "Meanings: bequeath, leave behind, reserve\nOnyomi: イ, ユイ\nKunyomi: のこ.す"
  answers:
    - 遺
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-57df
  prompt: "Meanings: range, region, limits\nOnyomi: イキ"
  answers:
    - 域
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5b87
  prompt: "Meanings: eaves, roof, house\nOnyomi: ウ"
  answers:
    - 宇
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6620
  prompt: "Meanings: reflect, reflection, projection\nOnyomi: エイ\nKunyomi: うつ.る, うつ.す, は.える, -ば.え"
  answers:
    - 映
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5ef6
  prompt: "Meanings: prolong, stretching\nOnyomi: エン\nKunyomi: の.びる, の.べる, の.べ, の.ばす"
  answers:
    - 延
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6cbf
  prompt: "Meanings: run alongside, follow along, run along\nOnyomi: エン\nKunyomi: そ.う, -ぞ.い"
  answers:
    - 沿
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6069
  prompt: "Meanings: grace, kindness, goodness\nOnyomi: オン"
  answers:
    - 恩
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6211
  prompt: "Meanings: ego, I, selfish\nOnyomi: ガ\nKunyomi: われ, わ, わ.が-, わが-"
  answers:
    - 我
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7070
  prompt: "Meanings: ashes, puckery juice, cremate\nOnyomi: カイ\nKunyomi: はい"
  answers:
    - 灰
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-62e1
  prompt: "Meanings: broaden, extend, expand\nOnyomi: カク, コウ\nKunyomi: ひろ.がる, ひろ.げる, ひろ.める"
  answers:
    - 拡
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-9769
  prompt: "Meanings: leather, skin, reform\nOnyomi: カク\nKunyomi: かわ"
  answers:
    - 革
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-95a3
  prompt: "Meanings: tower, tall building, palace\nOnyomi: カク"
  answers:
    - 閣
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5272
  prompt: "Meanings: proportion, comparatively, divide\nOnyomi: カツ\nKunyomi: わ.る, わり, わ.り, わ.れる"
  answers:
    - 割
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-682a
  prompt: "Meanings: stocks, stump, shares\nOnyomi: シュ\nKunyomi: かぶ"
  answers:
    - 株
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5e72
  prompt: "Meanings: dry, parch, ebb\nOnyomi: カン\nKunyomi: ほ.す, ほ.し-, -ぼ.し, ひ.る"
  answers:
    - 干
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5dfb
  prompt: "Meanings: scroll, volume, book\nOnyomi: カン, ケン\nKunyomi: ま.く, まき, ま.き"
  answers:
    - 巻
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-770b
  prompt: "Meanings: watch over, see\nOnyomi: カン\nKunyomi: み.る"
  answers:
    - 看
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7c21
  prompt: "Meanings: simplicity, brevity\nOnyomi: カン, ケン\nKunyomi: えら.ぶ, ふだ"
  answers:
    - 簡
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5371
  prompt: "Meanings: dangerous, fear, uneasy\nOnyomi: キ\nKunyomi: あぶ.ない, あや.うい, あや.ぶむ"
  answers:
    - 危
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-673a
  prompt: "Meanings: desk, table\nOnyomi: キ\nKunyomi: つくえ"
  answers:
    - 机
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-63ee
  prompt: "Meanings: brandish, wave, wag\nOnyomi: キ\nKunyomi: ふる.う"
  answers:
    - 揮
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8cb4
  prompt: "Meanings: precious, value, prize\nOnyomi: キ\nKunyomi: たっと.い, とうと.い, たっと.ぶ, とうと.ぶ"
  answers:
    - 貴
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7591
  prompt: "Meanings: doubt, distrust, be suspicious\nOnyomi: ギ\nKunyomi: うたが.う"
  answers:
    - 疑
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5438
  prompt: "Meanings: suck, imbibe, inhale\nOnyomi: キュウ\nKunyomi: す.う"
  answers:
    - 吸
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-4f9b
  prompt: "Meanings: submit, offer, present\nOnyomi: キョウ, ク, クウ, グ\nKunyomi: そな.える, とも, -ども"
  answers:
    - 供
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-80f8
  prompt: "Meanings: bosom, breast, chest\nOnyomi: キョウ\nKunyomi: むね, むな-"
  answers:
    - 胸
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-90f7
  prompt: "Meanings: home town, village, native place\nOnyomi: キョウ, ゴウ\nKunyomi: さと"
  answers:
    - 郷
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-52e4
  prompt: "Meanings: diligence, become employed, serve\nOnyomi: キン, ゴン\nKunyomi: つと.める, -づと.め, つと.まる, いそ.しむ"
  answers:
    - 勤
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7b4b
  prompt: "Meanings: muscle, sinew, tendon\nOnyomi: キン\nKunyomi: すじ"
  answers:
    - 筋
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7cfb
  prompt: "Meanings: lineage, system\nOnyomi: ケイ"
  answers:
    - 系
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-656c
  prompt: "Meanings: awe, respect, honor\nOnyomi: ケイ, キョウ\nKunyomi: うやま.う"
  answers:
    - 敬
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8b66
  prompt: "Meanings: admonish, commandment\nOnyomi: ケイ\nKunyomi: いまし.める"
  answers:
    - 警
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5287
  prompt: "Meanings: drama, play\nOnyomi: ゲキ"
  answers:
    - 劇
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6fc0
  prompt: "Meanings: violent, get excited, enraged\nOnyomi: ゲキ\nKunyomi: はげ.しい"
  answers:
    - 激
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7a74
  prompt: "Meanings: hole, aperture, slit\nOnyomi: ケツ\nKunyomi: あな"
  answers:
    - 穴
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5238
  prompt: "Meanings: ticket\nOnyomi: ケン"
  answers:
    - 券
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7d79
  prompt: "Meanings: silk\nOnyomi: ケン\nKunyomi: きぬ"
  answers:
    - 絹
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6a29
  prompt: "Meanings: authority, power, rights\nOnyomi: ケン, ゴン\nKunyomi: おもり, かり, はか.る"
  answers:
    - 権
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-61b2
  prompt: "Meanings: constitution, law\nOnyomi: ケン"
  answers:
    - 憲
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6e90
  prompt: "Meanings: source, origin\nOnyomi: ゲン\nKunyomi: みなもと"
  answers:
    - 源
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-53b3
  prompt: "Meanings: stern, strictness, severity\nOnyomi: ゲン, ゴン\nKunyomi: おごそ.か, きび.しい, いか.めしい, いつくし"
  answers:
    - 厳
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5df1
  prompt: "Meanings: self\nOnyomi: コ, キ\nKunyomi: おのれ, つちのと, な"
  answers:
    - 己
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-547c
  prompt: "Meanings: call, call out to, invite\nOnyomi: コ\nKunyomi: よ.ぶ"
  answers:
    - 呼
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8aa4
  prompt: "Meanings: mistake, err, do wrong\nOnyomi: ゴ\nKunyomi: あやま.る, -あやま.る"
  answers:
    - 誤
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-540e
  prompt: "Meanings: empress, queen, after\nOnyomi: コウ, ゴ\nKunyomi: きさき"
  answers:
    - 后
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5b5d
  prompt: "Meanings: filial piety, child's respect\nOnyomi: コウ, キョウ"
  answers:
    - 孝
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7687
  prompt: "Meanings: emperor\nOnyomi: コウ, オウ"
  answers:
    - 皇
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7d05
  prompt: "Meanings: crimson, deep red\nOnyomi: コウ, ク\nKunyomi: べに, くれない, あか.い"
  answers:
    - 紅
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-964d
  prompt: "Meanings: descend, precipitate, fall\nOnyomi: コウ, ゴ\nKunyomi: お.りる, お.ろす, ふ.る, ふ.り"
  answers:
    - 降
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-92fc
  prompt: "Meanings: steel\nOnyomi: コウ\nKunyomi: はがね"
  answers:
    - 鋼
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-523b
  prompt: "Meanings: engrave, cut fine, chop\nOnyomi: コク\nKunyomi: きざ.む, きざ.み"
  answers:
    - 刻
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7a40
  prompt: "Meanings: cereals, grain\nOnyomi: コク"
  answers:
    - 穀
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-9aa8
  prompt: "Meanings: skeleton, bone, remains\nOnyomi: コツ\nKunyomi: ほね"
  answers:
    - 骨
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-56f0
  prompt: "Meanings: quandary, become distressed, annoyed\nOnyomi: コン\nKunyomi: こま.る"
  answers:
    - 困
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7802
  prompt: "Meanings: sand\nOnyomi: サ, シャ\nKunyomi: すな"
  answers:
    - 砂
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5ea7
  prompt: "Meanings: squat, seat, cushion\nOnyomi: ザ\nKunyomi: すわ.る"
  answers:
    - 座
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6e08
  prompt: "Meanings: settle (debt, etc.), relieve (burden), finish\nOnyomi: サイ, セイ\nKunyomi: す.む, -ず.み, -ずみ, す.まない"
  answers:
    - 済
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-88c1
  prompt: "Meanings: tailor, judge, decision\nOnyomi: サイ\nKunyomi: た.つ, さば.く"
  answers:
    - 裁
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7b56
  prompt: "Meanings: scheme, plan, policy\nOnyomi: サク"
  answers:
    - 策
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-518a
  prompt: "Meanings: tome, counter for books, volume\nOnyomi: サツ, サク\nKunyomi: ふみ"
  answers:
    - 冊
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8695
  prompt: "Meanings: silkworm\nOnyomi: サン, テン\nKunyomi: かいこ, こ"
  answers:
    - 蚕
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-81f3
  prompt: "Meanings: climax, arrive, proceed\nOnyomi: シ\nKunyomi: いた.る"
  answers:
    - 至
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-79c1
  prompt: "Meanings: private, I, me\nOnyomi: シ\nKunyomi: わたくし, わたし"
  answers:
    - 私
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-59ff
  prompt: "Meanings: figure, form, shape\nOnyomi: シ\nKunyomi: すがた"
  answers:
    - 姿
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8996
  prompt: "Meanings: inspection, regard as, see\nOnyomi: シ\nKunyomi: み.る"
  answers:
    - 視
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8a5e
  prompt: "Meanings: part of speech, words, poetry\nOnyomi: シ\nKunyomi: ことば"
  answers:
    - 詞
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8a8c
  prompt: "Meanings: document, records\nOnyomi: シ"
  answers:
    - 誌
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-78c1
  prompt: "Meanings: magnet, porcelain\nOnyomi: ジ"
  answers:
    - 磁
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5c04
  prompt: "Meanings: shoot, shine into, onto\nOnyomi: シャ\nKunyomi: い.る, さ.す, う.つ"
  answers:
    - 射
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6368
  prompt: "Meanings: discard, throw away, abandon\nOnyomi: シャ\nKunyomi: す.てる"
  answers:
    - 捨
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5c3a
  prompt: "Meanings: shaku, Japanese foot, measure\nOnyomi: シャク, セキ\nKunyomi: さし"
  answers:
    - 尺
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-82e5
  prompt: "Meanings: young, if, perhaps\nOnyomi: ジャク, ニャク, ニャ\nKunyomi: わか.い, わか-, も.しくわ, も.し"
  answers:
    - 若
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6a39
  prompt: "Meanings: timber, trees, wood\nOnyomi: ジュ\nKunyomi: き"
  answers:
    - 樹
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-53ce
  prompt: "Meanings: income, obtain, reap\nOnyomi: シュウ\nKunyomi: おさ.める, おさ.まる"
  answers:
    - 収
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5b97
  prompt: "Meanings: religion, sect, denomination\nOnyomi: シュウ, ソウ\nKunyomi: むね"
  answers:
    - 宗
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5c31
  prompt: "Meanings: concerning, settle, take position\nOnyomi: シュウ, ジュ\nKunyomi: つ.く, つ.ける"
  answers:
    - 就
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8846
  prompt: "Meanings: masses, great numbers, multitude\nOnyomi: シュウ, シュ\nKunyomi: おお.い"
  answers:
    - 衆
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5f93
  prompt: "Meanings: accompany, obey, submit to\nOnyomi: ジュウ, ショウ, ジュ\nKunyomi: したが.う, したが.える, より"
  answers:
    - 従
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7e26
  prompt: "Meanings: vertical, length, height\nOnyomi: ジュウ\nKunyomi: たて"
  answers:
    - 縦
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7e2e
  prompt: "Meanings: shrink, contract, shrivel\nOnyomi: シュク\nKunyomi: ちぢ.む, ちぢ.まる, ちぢ.める, ちぢ.れる"
  answers:
    - 縮
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-719f
  prompt: "Meanings: mellow, ripen, mature\nOnyomi: ジュク\nKunyomi: う.れる"
  answers:
    - 熟
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7d14
  prompt: "Meanings: genuine, purity, innocence\nOnyomi: ジュン"
  answers:
    - 純
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-51e6
  prompt: "Meanings: dispose, manage, deal with\nOnyomi: ショ\nKunyomi: ところ, -こ, お.る"
  answers:
    - 処
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7f72
  prompt: "Meanings: signature, govt office, police station\nOnyomi: ショ"
  answers:
    - 署
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8af8
  prompt: "Meanings: various, many, several\nOnyomi: ショ\nKunyomi: もろ"
  answers:
    - 諸
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-9664
  prompt: "Meanings: exclude, division (x/3), remove\nOnyomi: ジョ, ジ\nKunyomi: のぞ.く, -よ.け"
  answers:
    - 除
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-627f
  prompt: "Meanings: acquiesce, hear, listen to\nOnyomi: ショウ, ジョウ\nKunyomi: うけたまわ.る, う.ける"
  answers:
    - 承
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5c06
  prompt: "Meanings: leader, commander, general\nOnyomi: ショウ, ソウ\nKunyomi: まさ.に, はた, まさ, ひきい.る"
  answers:
    - 将
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-50b7
  prompt: "Meanings: wound, hurt, injure\nOnyomi: ショウ\nKunyomi: きず, いた.む, いた.める"
  answers:
    - 傷
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-969c
  prompt: "Meanings: hinder, hurt, harm\nOnyomi: ショウ\nKunyomi: さわ.る"
  answers:
    - 障
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-84b8
  prompt: "Meanings: steam, heat, sultry\nOnyomi: ジョウ, セイ\nKunyomi: む.す, む.れる, む.らす"
  answers:
    - 蒸
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-91dd
  prompt: "Meanings: needle, pin, staple\nOnyomi: シン\nKunyomi: はり"
  answers:
    - 針
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-4ec1
  prompt: "Meanings: humanity, virtue, benevolence\nOnyomi: ジン, ニ, ニン"
  answers:
    - 仁
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5782
  prompt: "Meanings: droop, suspend, hang\nOnyomi: スイ\nKunyomi: た.れる, た.らす, た.れ, -た.れ"
  answers:
    - 垂
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-63a8
  prompt: "Meanings: conjecture, infer, guess\nOnyomi: スイ\nKunyomi: お.す"
  answers:
    - 推
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5bf8
  prompt: "Meanings: measurement, tenth of a shaku, a little\nOnyomi: スン"
  answers:
    - 寸
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-76db
  prompt: "Meanings: boom, prosper, copulate\nOnyomi: セイ, ジョウ\nKunyomi: も.る, さか.る, さか.ん"
  answers:
    - 盛
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8056
  prompt: "Meanings: holy, saint, sage\nOnyomi: セイ, ショウ\nKunyomi: ひじり"
  answers:
    - 聖
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8aa0
  prompt: "Meanings: sincerity, admonish, warn\nOnyomi: セイ\nKunyomi: まこと"
  answers:
    - 誠
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-820c
  prompt: "Meanings: tongue, reed, clapper\nOnyomi: ゼツ\nKunyomi: した"
  answers:
    - 舌
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5ba3
  prompt: "Meanings: proclaim, say, announce\nOnyomi: セン\nKunyomi: のたま.う"
  answers:
    - 宣
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5c02
  prompt: "Meanings: specialty, exclusive, mainly\nOnyomi: セン\nKunyomi: もっぱ.ら"
  answers:
    - 専
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6cc9
  prompt: "Meanings: spring, fountain\nOnyomi: セン\nKunyomi: いずみ"
  answers:
    - 泉
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6d17
  prompt: "Meanings: wash, inquire into, probe\nOnyomi: セン\nKunyomi: あら.う"
  answers:
    - 洗
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-67d3
  prompt: "Meanings: dye, color, paint\nOnyomi: セン\nKunyomi: そ.める, そ.まる, し.みる, し.み"
  answers:
    - 染
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-92ad
  prompt: "Meanings: coin, .01 yen, money\nOnyomi: セン, ゼン\nKunyomi: ぜに, すき"
  answers:
    - 銭
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5584
  prompt: "Meanings: virtuous, good, goodness\nOnyomi: ゼン\nKunyomi: よ.い, い.い, よ.く, よし.とする"
  answers:
    - 善
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-594f
  prompt: "Meanings: play music, speak to a ruler, complete\nOnyomi: ソウ\nKunyomi: かな.でる"
  answers:
    - 奏
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7a93
  prompt: "Meanings: window, pane\nOnyomi: ソウ, ス\nKunyomi: まど, てんまど, けむだし"
  answers:
    - 窓
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5275
  prompt: "Meanings: genesis, wound, injury\nOnyomi: ソウ, ショウ\nKunyomi: つく.る, はじ.める, きず, けず.しける"
  answers:
    - 創
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-88c5
  prompt: "Meanings: attire, dress, pretend\nOnyomi: ソウ, ショウ\nKunyomi: よそお.う, よそお.い"
  answers:
    - 装
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5c64
  prompt: "Meanings: stratum, social class, layer\nOnyomi: ソウ"
  answers:
    - 層
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-64cd
  prompt: "Meanings: maneuver, manipulate, operate\nOnyomi: ソウ, サン\nKunyomi: みさお, あやつ.る"
  answers:
    - 操
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8535
  prompt: "Meanings: storehouse, hide, own\nOnyomi: ゾウ, ソウ\nKunyomi: くら, おさ.める, かく.れる"
  answers:
    - 蔵
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-81d3
  prompt: "Meanings: entrails, viscera, bowels\nOnyomi: ゾウ\nKunyomi: はらわた"
  answers:
    - 臓
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5b58
  prompt: "Meanings: exist, suppose, be aware of\nOnyomi: ソン, ゾン\nKunyomi: ながら.える, あ.る, たも.つ, と.う"
  answers:
    - 存
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5c0a
  prompt: "Meanings: revered, valuable, precious\nOnyomi: ソン\nKunyomi: たっと.い, とうと.い, たっと.ぶ, とうと.ぶ"
  answers:
    - 尊
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-9000
  prompt: "Meanings: retreat, withdraw, retire\nOnyomi: タイ\nKunyomi: しりぞ.く, しりぞ.ける, ひ.く, の.く"
  answers:
    - 退
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5b85
  prompt: "Meanings: home, house, residence\nOnyomi: タク"
  answers:
    - 宅
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-62c5
  prompt: "Meanings: shouldering, carry, raise\nOnyomi: タン\nKunyomi: かつ.ぐ, にな.う"
  answers:
    - 担
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-63a2
  prompt: "Meanings: grope, search, look for\nOnyomi: タン\nKunyomi: さぐ.る, さが.す"
  answers:
    - 探
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8a95
  prompt: "Meanings: nativity, be born, declension\nOnyomi: タン"
  answers:
    - 誕
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6bb5
  prompt: "Meanings: grade, steps, stairs\nOnyomi: ダン, タン"
  answers:
    - 段
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6696
  prompt: "Meanings: warmth\nOnyomi: ダン, ノン\nKunyomi: あたた.か, あたた.かい, あたた.まる, あたた.める"
  answers:
    - 暖
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5024
  prompt: "Meanings: price, cost, value\nOnyomi: チ\nKunyomi: ね, あたい"
  answers:
    - 値
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5b99
  prompt: "Meanings: mid-air, air, space\nOnyomi: チュウ"
  answers:
    - 宙
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5fe0
  prompt: "Meanings: loyalty, fidelity, faithfulness\nOnyomi: チュウ"
  answers:
    - 忠
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8457
  prompt: "Meanings: renowned, publish, write\nOnyomi: チョ, チャク\nKunyomi: あらわ.す, いちじる.しい"
  answers:
    - 著
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5e81
  prompt: "Meanings: government office\nOnyomi: チョウ, テイ\nKunyomi: やくしょ"
  answers:
    - 庁
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-9802
  prompt: "Meanings: place on the head, receive, top of head\nOnyomi: チョウ\nKunyomi: いただ.く, いただき"
  answers:
    - 頂
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8178
  prompt: "Meanings: intestines, guts, bowels\nOnyomi: チョウ\nKunyomi: はらわた, わた"
  answers:
    - 腸
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6f6e
  prompt: "Meanings: tide, salt water, opportunity\nOnyomi: チョウ\nKunyomi: しお, うしお"
  answers:
    - 潮
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8cc3
  prompt: "Meanings: fare, fee, hire\nOnyomi: チン"
  answers:
    - 賃
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-75db
  prompt: "Meanings: pain, hurt, damage\nOnyomi: ツウ\nKunyomi: いた.い, いた.む, いた.ましい, いた.める"
  answers:
    - 痛
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6575
  prompt: "Meanings: enemy, foe, opponent\nOnyomi: テキ\nKunyomi: かたき, あだ, かな.う"
  answers:
    - 敵
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5c55
  prompt: "Meanings: unfold, expand\nOnyomi: テン"
  answers:
    - 展
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8a0e
  prompt: "Meanings: chastise, attack, defeat\nOnyomi: トウ\nKunyomi: う.つ"
  answers:
    - 討
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-515a
  prompt: "Meanings: party, faction, clique\nOnyomi: トウ\nKunyomi: なかま, むら"
  answers:
    - 党
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7cd6
  prompt: "Meanings: sugar\nOnyomi: トウ"
  answers:
    - 糖
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5c4a
  prompt: "Meanings: deliver, reach, arrive\nOnyomi: カイ\nKunyomi: とど.ける, -とど.け, とど.く"
  answers:
    - 届
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-96e3
  prompt: "Meanings: difficult, impossible, trouble\nOnyomi: ナン\nKunyomi: かた.い, -がた.い, むずか.しい, むづか.しい"
  answers:
    - 難
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-4e73
  prompt: "Meanings: milk, breasts\nOnyomi: ニュウ\nKunyomi: ちち, ち"
  answers:
    - 乳
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8a8d
  prompt: "Meanings: acknowledge, witness, discern\nOnyomi: ニン\nKunyomi: みと.める, したた.める"
  answers:
    - 認
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7d0d
  prompt: "Meanings: settlement, obtain, reap\nOnyomi: ノウ, ナッ, ナ, ナン\nKunyomi: おさ.める, -おさ.める, おさ.まる"
  answers:
    - 納
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8133
  prompt: "Meanings: brain, memory\nOnyomi: ノウ, ドウ\nKunyomi: のうずる"
  answers:
    - 脳
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6d3e
  prompt: "Meanings: faction, group, party\nOnyomi: ハ"
  answers:
    - 派
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-62dd
  prompt: "Meanings: worship, adore, pray to\nOnyomi: ハイ\nKunyomi: おが.む, おろが.む"
  answers:
    - 拝
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-80cc
  prompt: "Meanings: stature, height, back\nOnyomi: ハイ\nKunyomi: せ, せい, そむ.く, そむ.ける"
  answers:
    - 背
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-80ba
  prompt: "Meanings: lungs\nOnyomi: ハイ"
  answers:
    - 肺
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-4ff3
  prompt: "Meanings: haiku, actor\nOnyomi: ハイ"
  answers:
    - 俳
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-73ed
  prompt: "Meanings: squad, corps, unit\nOnyomi: ハン"
  answers:
    - 班
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6669
  prompt: "Meanings: nightfall, night\nOnyomi: バン"
  answers:
    - 晩
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5426
  prompt: "Meanings: negate, no, noes\nOnyomi: ヒ\nKunyomi: いな, いや"
  answers:
    - 否
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6279
  prompt: "Meanings: criticism, strike\nOnyomi: ヒ"
  answers:
    - 批
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-79d8
  prompt: "Meanings: secret, conceal\nOnyomi: ヒ\nKunyomi: ひ.める, ひそ.か, かく.す"
  answers:
    - 秘
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-4ff5
  prompt: "Meanings: bag, bale, sack\nOnyomi: ヒョウ\nKunyomi: たわら"
  answers:
    - 俵
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8179
  prompt: "Meanings: abdomen, belly, stomach\nOnyomi: フク\nKunyomi: はら"
  answers:
    - 腹
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-596e
  prompt: "Meanings: stirred up, be invigorated, flourish\nOnyomi: フン\nKunyomi: ふる.う"
  answers:
    - 奮
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-4e26
  prompt: "Meanings: row, and, besides\nOnyomi: ヘイ, ホウ\nKunyomi: な.み, なみ, なら.べる, なら.ぶ"
  answers:
    - 並
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-965b
  prompt: "Meanings: highness, steps (of throne)\nOnyomi: ヘイ"
  answers:
    - 陛
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-9589
  prompt: "Meanings: closed, shut\nOnyomi: ヘイ\nKunyomi: と.じる, と.ざす, し.める, し.まる"
  answers:
    - 閉
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7247
  prompt: "Meanings: one-sided, leaf, sheet\nOnyomi: ヘン\nKunyomi: かた-, かた"
  answers:
    - 片
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-88dc
  prompt: "Meanings: supplement, supply, make good\nOnyomi: ホ\nKunyomi: おぎな.う"
  answers:
    - 補
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-66ae
  prompt: "Meanings: evening, twilight, season's end\nOnyomi: ボ\nKunyomi: く.れる, く.らす"
  answers:
    - 暮
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5b9d
  prompt: "Meanings: treasure, wealth, valuables\nOnyomi: ホウ\nKunyomi: たから"
  answers:
    - 宝
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8a2a
  prompt: "Meanings: call on, visit, look up\nOnyomi: ホウ\nKunyomi: おとず.れる, たず.ねる, と.う"
  answers:
    - 訪
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-4ea1
  prompt: "Meanings: deceased, the late, dying\nOnyomi: ボウ, モウ\nKunyomi: な.い, な.き-, ほろ.びる, ほろ.ぶ"
  answers:
    - 亡
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5fd8
  prompt: "Meanings: forget\nOnyomi: ボウ\nKunyomi: わす.れる"
  answers:
    - 忘
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-68d2
  prompt: "Meanings: rod, stick, cane\nOnyomi: ボウ"
  answers:
    - 棒
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-679a
  prompt: "Meanings: sheet of..., counter for flat thin objects or sheets\nOnyomi: マイ, バイ"
  answers:
    - 枚
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5e55
  prompt: "Meanings: curtain, bunting, act of play\nOnyomi: マク, バク\nKunyomi: とばり"
  answers:
    - 幕
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5bc6
  prompt: "Meanings: secrecy, density (pop), minuteness\nOnyomi: ミツ\nKunyomi: ひそ.か"
  answers:
    - 密
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-76df
  prompt: "Meanings: alliance, oath\nOnyomi: メイ"
  answers:
    - 盟
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6a21
  prompt: "Meanings: imitation, copy, mock\nOnyomi: モ, ボ"
  answers:
    - 模
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8a33
  prompt: "Meanings: translate, reason, circumstance\nOnyomi: ヤク\nKunyomi: わけ"
  answers:
    - 訳
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-90f5
  prompt: "Meanings: mail, stagecoach stop\nOnyomi: ユウ"
  answers:
    - 郵
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-512a
  prompt: "Meanings: tenderness, excel, surpass\nOnyomi: ユウ, ウ\nKunyomi: やさ.しい, すぐ.れる, まさ.る"
  answers:
    - 優
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-9810
  prompt: "Meanings: deposit, custody, leave with\nOnyomi: ヨ\nKunyomi: あず.ける, あず.かる"
  answers:
    - 預
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5e7c
  prompt: "Meanings: infancy, childhood\nOnyomi: ヨウ\nKunyomi: おさな.い"
  answers:
    - 幼
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6b32
  prompt: "Meanings: longing, covetousness, greed\nOnyomi: ヨク\nKunyomi: ほっ.する, ほ.しい"
  answers:
    - 欲
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7fcc
  prompt: "Meanings: the following, next\nOnyomi: ヨク"
  answers:
    - 翌
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-4e71
  prompt: "Meanings: riot, war, disorder\nOnyomi: ラン, ロン\nKunyomi: みだ.れる, みだ.る, みだ.す, みだ"
  answers:
    - 乱
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5375
  prompt: "Meanings: egg, ovum, spawn\nOnyomi: ラン\nKunyomi: たまご"
  answers:
    - 卵
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-89a7
  prompt: "Meanings: perusal, see\nOnyomi: ラン\nKunyomi: み.る"
  answers:
    - 覧
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-88cf
  prompt: "Meanings: back, amidst, in\nOnyomi: リ\nKunyomi: うら"
  answers:
    - 裏
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5f8b
  prompt: "Meanings: rhythm, law, regulation\nOnyomi: リツ, リチ, レツ"
  answers:
    - 律
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-81e8
  prompt: "Meanings: look to, face, meet\nOnyomi: リン\nKunyomi: のぞ.む"
  answers:
    - 臨
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6717
  prompt: "Meanings: melodious, clear, bright\nOnyomi: ロウ\nKunyomi: ほが.らか, あき.らか"
  answers:
    - 朗
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8ad6
  prompt: "Meanings: argument, discourse\nOnyomi: ロン\nKunyomi: あげつら.う"
  answers:
    - 論
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []
